{
    "subject": "resource/Santosh_Shukla",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Santosh Shukla is an Indian bollywood film and television actor. He raised fame after his stint in Bigg Boss 6. Shukla made his Bollywood debut from film Jai Ho - released in 2014.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Santosh Shukla says that he is an Indian bollywood film and television actor, who gained fame after being on Bigg Boss 6, and also mentions that he made his Bollywood debut with the movie Jai Ho released in 2014.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.893269956111908,
            "question": "What was the title of Santosh Shukla's Bollywood debut movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.885546088218689,
            "question": "What year did Santosh Shukla make his Bollywood debut?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8176664710044861,
            "question": "What movie marked Santosh Shukla's entry into Bollywood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7852945923805237,
            "question": "Is Santosh Shukla known for film and television work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7570710778236389,
            "question": "In what type of entertainment industry did Santosh Shukla gain fame?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.690927267074585,
            "question": "Where did Santosh Shukla become famous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6429598331451416,
            "question": "What is Santosh Shukla's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6182265877723694,
            "question": "What nationality is Santosh Shukla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5490339994430542,
            "question": "Which reality show helped Santosh Shukla gain recognition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5428157448768616,
            "question": "Did Santosh Shukla appear in a reality show?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Santosh Shukla says that he is an Indian bollywood film and television actor, who gained fame after being on Bigg Boss 6, and also mentions that he made his Bollywood debut with the movie Jai Ho released in 2014.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8567_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which reality show helped Santosh Shukla gain recognition?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8567_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Santosh Shukla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8567_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Santosh Shukla's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8567_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8567_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents indeed support the statement about Santosh Shukla. They confirm that he is an Indian actor who gained fame after his stint on Bigg Boss 6 and made his Bollywood debut with the film Jai Ho, which was released in 2014."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}